

# **Anatoly Pauk**

### Contact

#### **Address**

Str, Shkalova 38, Artsyz, Odessa Oblast

#### Skype

live:.cid.4e9874a1128db3f7

#### **Email**

anatoliyp703@gmail.com

#### Skills

- Development Languages(Python, PHP)
- Database and cache(MySQL, MongoDB, Oracle, SQLServer)
- Server (Apache, Nginx, IIS servers)
  - API (REST & SOAP)
- Algorithms and data structures

## Senior Back-end Developer

My name is Anatoly Pauk and I have experience for 7+ years in the backend development.

My skills:

Development Languages(Python, PHP)
Database and cache(MySQL, MongoDB, Oracle, SQLServer)
Server (Apache, Nginx, IIS servers)
API (REST & SOAP) Development
Algorithms and data structures

My experience and responsibility are:

Development Specialist with 7 years of industry experience and knowledge of onboarding and training employees, effectively planning strategies to meet staff development requirements. Experienced in using learning management systems. Drives training and development across all levels of the company.

Self-motivated Web Developer with a high level of experience working on multiple projects. Passionate and hardworking with a penchant for meeting deadlines. Interested in role with the company promoting best practices and offering diverse customer projects.

Logical and results-driven Web Developer dedicated to building and optimizing user-focused websites for customers with various business objectives. Judicious and creative when crafting effective websites, apps, and platforms to propel competitive advantage and revenue growth. Technically proficient and analytical problem solver with a calm and focused demeanor.

## Work Experience

04/2008 - 07/2019

## OJSC "Odessa Gas"

System Administrator

- Established network specifications and analyzed workflow, access, information and security requirements
- Implemented, developed and tested installation and update of file servers, print servers and application servers in all departments
- Standardized job tasks and trained junior team members on industry best practices and standards

08/2019 - 12/2019

## Upwork

Selenium/Firefox/Php Expert Needed to Create Login

I am looking for a developer to write a script that logs into Facebook, saves a cookie so that I don't need to log in again. That's all. Simple. But it needs do be scripted in Selenium / Firefox / Php, no exception. Thank you

## Education

# Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute

Bachelor of Engineering (B.Eng.), Mechanical engineering

07/2008 - 08/2012

#### **Internet Course**

I studied back end skills by myself on Internet Course. And I have got good experience in several projects.

# Languages

English — A3

Ukraine — B3